Beschrijving van de collection Cornelis Hendrik van Schooneveld
Universiteitsbibliotheek Leiden
- Archives regarding Mouton and related activities (inv. nos. 1-13)., A.
  - Mouton editor's correspondence., 1.; Correspondence, in alphabetical order by name, concerning manuscripts that were earmarked for publication in the Mouton series Slavistic printings and reprintings, Janua linguarum and De proprietatibus litterarum.; 97 boxes.; Every manuscript (in some case th
    - C
      509. Calbert, J.P. (Dimensions of style and meaning in the language of Trakl and Rilke). - 510. Caldwell, S. - 511. Caldwell, W.V. - 512. Calimag, E. de Lara - 513. Calin, F. - 514. Calinescu, G. - 515. Callaghan, C.A. - 516. Callicott, J.B. (Plato’s aesthetics and introduction to the theory of forms). - 517. Calvano, W.J. (Synchronic relationships: five Romance dialects). - 518. Camara, M. - 519. vacant. - 520. Campbell, R.J. - 521. Campbell, R.N. - 522. Campen, J.A. van - 523. Campo, H. de - 524. Cannon, G. (An integrated transformational grammar of the English language). - 525. Cantrall, W. - 526. Cantrall, W.R. - 527. Cantrall, W.R. (Fully recursive syntax). - 528. Capell, A. (Maung). - 529. Capell, A. (Studies in soc-ling.). - 530. Capell, A. (Studies in socio-Linguistics). - 531. Caporale, R. - 532. Caprio, D.C. (Jules Laforgue’s ‘Le concile séerique’: a stylistic structural analysis). - 533. Carbo, N.A. (The mind and the muse). - 534. vacant. - 535. Cardaillac-Kelly, R. - 536. Cardona, G. - 537. Cardona, G. - 538. Cardona, G. (Pān.ini). - 539. Carey, C. - 540. Carey, P.W. - 541. Carkeet, D.C. (An Old English syntactic constraint). - 542. Carleton, F.B. (The dramatic monologue: vox humana). - 543. Carlos, L.B. - 544. Carlton, C.M. - 545. Carlton, C.R. - 546. Carney, E. - 547. Carpenter, C.W. - 548. Carpenter, R.H. - 549. Carr, A. - 550. Carrington, L.D. - 551. Carrington, S.M. Jr. - 552. Carroll, J.B. - 553. Carson, J.A. (The linguist and literature: a critical examination of contemporary theories). - 554. Carter, C.L. (Style, painting and language: a study of language-like features of painting). - 555. Carter, T.P. (Encyclopedia of terms used in foreign language teaching). - 556. Cartledge, S.J. - 557. Carvell, H.T., and J. Svartvik - 558. Carvell, H.T., and J. Svartvik - 559. Carver, George Lafayette - 560. Casagrande, J. (ed.) (Symposium on Romance languages). - 561. Cascio, V. Lo - 562. Casher, Asa - 563. Cassidy, Paul J. - 564. Cassirer, Peter - 565. Castle, William - 566. Catoline, J.E. (A comparative and structural analysis of the Français Fondamental vocabulary). - 567. Cattell, R. (Role of ‘give’ and related verbs in English). - 568. Cavanaugh, P.G. (Literary criticism of Sir Herbert Read). - 569. Cave, G.N. - 570. Cazacu, B. (Travaux des Colloques de Linguistique). - 571. Cazacu, T. - 572. Celce-Murcia, M. (A syntactic and psycholinguistic study of comparison in English). - 573. Celler, M.M. - 574. Cervenka, E.J. - 575. Cevera, M.B. (Distinctive phonology of Lhasa Central Tibetan). - 576. Chadderdon, A.H. - 577. Chafe, W.L. (Collection of articles). - 578. Chai, N.M. - 579. Chambers, J.K. - 580. Chamot, A. - 581. Champagne, R.A. (Beyond the structuralist myth of ‘écriture’). - 582. Champigny, R. - 583. Champigny, R. (Ontologie du narratif). - 584. Chan, J.Y.-M. - 585. Chan, R.K. - 586. Chandola, A.C. - 587. Channon, R. - 588. Chao, Y.R. - 589. Chao, Y.R. (Collection of articles). - 590. Chaplin, M.J. (Michail Prišvin). - 591. Chapman, R.S. (Interpretation of deviant sentences ). - 592. Chappel, A.H. - 593. Chappel, A.H. - 594. Chardžiev, N. (Russkie kubo-futuristy...). - 595. Chardžiev, N. (Russkie kubo-futuristy...). - 596. sister Peter Damian Charles O.P. - 597. Chatman, S.B. (Articles). - 598. Chatman, S.B. - 599. Chatman, S.B. (The style of Henry James). - 600. Chatman, S.B. (Theory of narrative structure). - 601. Chayen, M.J. (Phonetics of Israeli Hebrew). - 602. Chen, M. (Nasals and nasalization in Chinese). - 603. Cheng, R.L. - 604. Cherniss, M.D. - 605. Chew, J.J. Jr. - 606. Chiang, H.T. - 607. Chisholm, D. - 608. Chisholm, D.H. - 609. Chisholm, W.S. - 610. Chlebnikova, I.B. (Soslagatel’noe naklonenie v anglijskom jazyke). - 611. Chlebnikova, I.B. - 612. Cho, Seung-bog - 613. Chojko-Boutière, J. - 614. vacant - 615. Chomsky, N. (Conditions on transformations). - 616. Chomsky, N. (Current issues in linguistic theory). - 617. Chomsky, N. (Logical structure of linguistic theory). - 618. Chomsky, N. (Semantics). - 619. Chomsky, N. (Syntactic structures). - 620. Chomsky, N. (Topics in the theory of generative grammar). - 621. Christa, B. - 622. Christoff, P.K. - 623. Christoff, P.K. (Chomjakov). - 624. Christoff, P.K. - 625. Christoff, P.K. (Kireevskij volume). - 626. Chumbow, B.S. (Rule Complication as a Mechanism of Linguistic Change). - 627. Church, C.E. - 628. Čičerin, B.N. - 629. Cienciala, A. (ed.) (American contributions to the Warsaw Congress: III Hist.). - 630. Cintas, P.F. (The syntactic derivation of French adjectives). - 631. Cioran, S.D. - 632. Cioran, S.D. (Vladimir Solov’ev and the Russian Sophiologists). - 633. Cisar, M.A. (The Image of the self: Autobiographical Space in the Works of Madame Roland). - 633bis Civera, Marco Bernard (Distinctive phonology). - 634. Čiževska, T. - 635. Čiževskij, D. - 636. Čizevskij, D. (Hist. of Ukrain. lit.). - 637. Čizevskij, D. (History of Russian literature). - 638. Čizevskij, D. (Ost und West). - 639. Čizevskij, D. (Ost und West). - 640. Čizevskij, D. (Slav. series). - 641. Clardy, J. - 642. Clark, E.V. - 643. Clark, H. - 644. Clark, H.H. (Selected writings). - 645. Clark, H.H. (Semantics; Comprehension). - 646. Clark, L.V. (Bibliographical guide to Turkic linguistics). - 647. Clark, R.A. - 648. Clark, R.A. - 649. Clark, S. - 650. Clarke, B.L. - 651. Clas, A. (Colloquium on linguistics...). - 652. Cleary, C. (Introduction to the life and works of Dancourt). - 653. Clegg, J.S. - 654. Clevenger, T. Jr. - 655. Clifford, J.E. (Tense and tense logic). - 656. Clifton, C.E. Jr. - 657. Cline, W. J. (The phonology of 16th century American Spanish). - 658. Clivio, G. - 659. Closs, E. - 660. Coady, J.M. (The Utilization of...). - 661. Coates, P. - 662. Cobau, W.W. - 663. Cockrell, C.R.S. (Volume on Pushkin). - 664. Coe, R.M. (Contemporary critical method, ideology, science, and reality.). - 665. Coffin, A.R. - 666. Cohen, D. (Études de linguistique). - 667. Cohen, D. (Mélanges Marcel Cohen). - 668. Cohen, D. (Parler arabe). - 669. Cohen, D. Jr. (Actes du congrès). - 670. Cohen, J.E. - 671. Cohen, J.L. - 672. Cohn, D.C. - 673. Cohn, R. - 674. Cohn, R.G. (Writer’s way in France). - 675. Cole, P. - 676. Cole, P. (Indefiniteness and anaphoricity: the analogical extension of a semantically…). - 677. Cole, P. (editor) (Hebrew syntax and semantics: theoretical issues). - 678. Coleman, E.S. - 679. Coleman, R.O. - 680. Coleman, R.G. - 681. Collinge, N.E. - 682. Collins, C.T. - 683. Collins, C. (Zamjatin: interpretive study). - 684. Collins, F. - 685. Collins, J.D. (The Paston letters: a new approach to diachronic linguistic change). - 686. Collins, M.J. (Comedy in Renaissance love poetry: an essay on Sidney Drayton, Shakespeare, and Donne). - 687. Collins, T.J. - 688. Colson, J. (Criteria for a tentative definition of poetry). - 689. Coltharp, L.H. - 690. Colwell, F.S. - 691. Companys, S. (Manuel de phonétique corrective). - 692. Companys, S. (Manuel de phonologie comparée.). - 693. Compton, J.D. - 694. Compton, J.E. (A critique of Nathan A. Scott Jr.’s theological literary criticism). - 695. Conner, J. - 696. Connolly, M.J., and L. Jones (Translations of Jakobson art.). - 697. Contreras, H. (Indeterminate-subject-sentence in Sp.). - 697bis. Contreras, Helen (dissertation: The phonological system of a bilingual child) - 698. Cook, D.J. (The role of language in Hegel). - 699. Cook, M.J. - 700. Cook, W.A. - 701. Cook, W.A. - 702. Cooke, J.R. - 703. Cooke, T.D. - 704. Cooke, V.M. (Private language and public discourse: a study of Wittgenstein’s use of...). - 705. Coombs, V. - 706. Cooney, J.F. (Juan Luis Vives, De Ratione Dicendi…). - 707. Cooper, D.E. (Presupposition). - 708. Cooper, F.S. - 709. Cooper, W.S. - 710. Cooper, W.S. (The indefinite article of English: a case study in logico- linguistics). - 711. Copeland, H.C. (Art and the artist in the works of Samuel Beckett). - 712. Copeland, J.E. - 713. Cor, L.W. - 714. Cordonnier, M.E. - 715. Cormican, J.D. (Deep case model for Early Mod. English). - 716. Correll, T.C. - 717. Cortina- Comez, R. - 718. Coseriu, E. (Bedeutungsfelder). - 719. Coseriu, E. (Collected articles). - 720. Coseriu, E. (Collected works). - 721. Coseriu, E. (Linguistics and semantics). - 722. Cosman, M.P. - 723. Cosper, D. - 724. Costello, J.R. (A grammar of Old Frisian). - 725. Couch, W. (Medieval tragic mode in Middle English literature). - 726. Couchman, G.W. - 727. Coulmas, F. (Conversational routine). - 728. Couper-Kuhlen, E. (The prepositional passive in English). - 729. Courteville, Y. - 730. Coyaud, M. - 731. Craddock, G.E. Jr. - 732. Crandall, J.E. - 733. Crapo, R.H. - 734. Crapo, R.H. (Basic Quechua). - 735. Crawford, J.M. - 736. Crawley, T.E. - 737. Creed, R.P. - 738. Creeger, G. R. - 739. Crichfield, G. - 740. Cromer, R. - 741. Cronin, F.C. - 742. Crook, E.J. (Handbook of Middle English grammar: phonology of Richard Jordan). - 743. Crosby, D.A. - 744. Crosman, I.D. (Time metaphors). - 745. Crothers, E.J. (Paragraph structure description). - 746. Crowell, M.G. - 747. Crymes, R. - 748. Csipkés, G.K. (B. Korponay - ed.). - 749. Cudinskij, E. - 750. Čulík, K. - 751. Culley, R.C. - 752. Cummings, D.W. - 753. Cummings, M., and R. Simmons (The Language of literature). - 754. Cunningham, I.A.E. (Syntactic analysis of Sea Island Creole (‘Gullah’)). - 755. Cunningham, M.P. - 756. Cunningham, W.L. - 757. Curnier-Dorgon, P. - 758. Curran, M.W. (Art belongs to the people: Vladimir Stasov and National Russian art, 1850-1906). - 759. Curtis, A. - 760. Curtis, J.L. (Camus’ absurd hero). - 761. Cusac, M.E.H. - 762. Cushman, B.P. - 763. Cvetkova, L. S. (The restoration of speech and language in local brain). - 764. Czaplajewicz, E. - 765. Czochralski, Jan Antoni
    - D
      766. Dacus, T.L. (William Collins’ poetry: theory and practice compared to Joseph Warton’s). - 767. Daemmrich, I.G. (The ruins motif in French literature). - 768. Dagut, M.B. (A linguistic analysis of some semantic problems of Hebrew English translation). - 769. Dahlstedt, K.-H. - 770. Daltas, P. (Inflectional morphology of the verb in Modern Greek). - 771. Daly, J.P. - 772. Daly, R.T. (Applications of mathematical theory of linguistics). - 773. Damerau, F.J. - 774. Dane, J.A. (Res; Verba: A study in Medieval French drama). - 775. Daneš, F. (Functional sentence perspective). - 776. Danhauer, J. L., and S. Singh (A multidimensional analysis of hearing impaired subjects’ responses to sixteen). - 777. Daniel, M.L. - 778. Danzig, A.P. - 779. Daugman, J. - 780. Davidowitz, G. - 781. Davidson, D. (Collection of articles). - 782. Davies, J. - 783. Davis, J.E. - 784. Davis, M. - 785. Davis, P. - 786. Day, C.C. - 787. De Fazio, C.C. - 788. De Silva, M.W.S. - 789. Décsy, G. (ed.) (Soziolinguistik und die Sprache Europas). - 790. Dees, A. - 791. Defromont, H.J. (Verbe anglais contemporain). - 792. Delasanta, R. - 793. Delattre, P. - 794. Deligiorgis, S.G. - 795. Delisle, G.L. - 796. DeMan, P.M. - 797. Demand, N.H. - 798. Demarque, M.C. - 799. Demetrakapoulos, G.H. - 800. Deming, R.H. (‘Wilde Civility’: Herrick’s poetry). - 801. Deming, R.H. - 802. Demoz, A. (ed.) (Leslau Festschrift ). - 803. Denisov, P. N. - 804. Der-Houssikian, H. - 805. Derbyshire, W.W. - 806. Derden, J. K. Jr. (Analyticity and scientific theories with special ref. to work of R. Carnap). - 806bis. Derwing, Bruce (Traditional grammar and language acquisition. - 807. Despalatovič, E.M. - 808. Dessner, L.J. - 809. Detering, K. - 810. Deugd, C. de - 811. Devine, A.M. - 812. Devine, A.M. (Clusters). - 813. Devine, A.M. (Laboivelars). - 814. Devitt, M. (Designation). - 815. Devons, N. - 816. Devrnja, M.P. (The conceptions of human existence in the Early Works of F.M. Dostoevskii). - 817. Dew, J. - 818. Dezsö, L. - 819. Dezso, L. (Serbo-Croatian Syntax). - 820. Di Giovanna, J.J. (Linguistic phenomenology: philosophiscal method in J.L. Austin). - 821. Di Giovanna, J.J. (Notre Dame, Indiana Symposium, language; symbol; reality). - 822. Dial, R.L. - 823. Diamond, R.E. - 824. Diebold, A.R. Jr. - 825. Dieltjens, L.J. (Rule-governed creativity). - 826. Dietrich, R.F. - 827. Dijk, Teun van (Studies in the pragmatics of discourse). - 828. Dijk, Teun van (The Puerto Rico Lectures on the structures and functions of discourse). - 828bis. Dijk, Teun van (Some aspects of text grammars) - 829. Dillard, J.L. (Perspectives in Black English). - 830. Dimmler, G.R. - 831. Dingwall, William Orr - 832. Dinneen, D.A. - 833. DiPietro, R. - 834. Dirven, R. - 835. Dixon, P.W. (The ontology of language). - 836. Dixon, R.M.W. (Collection of essays semantics and syntax - where have all the adjectives gone?). 836bis. Dixon, R.M.W. (Linguistic sciences and logic). - 837. Djakonov, I.M. (The languages of the Ancient Near East). - 838. Dolan, P.J. - 839. Doležal, L. - 840. Doležal, L. - 841. Doležal, L. - 842. Dombrovsky, J. - 843. Dominick, L.A. - 844. Donaldson, W.D. - 845. Donchenko, A.K. (Bi-aspectual ovat’ verbs in Russian). - 846. Done, A.N. - 847. Dones, J.E. (A model for perception and language). - 848. Donohue, A.M. (Hawthorne: Calvin’s ironic stepchild). - 849. Donohue, J.W. Jr. - 850. Doorslaer, M.P. - 851. Dore, J. (The development of speech acts). - 852. Dorian, N.C. - 853. Dorner, S - 854. Dostal, A. (OCS texts). - 855. Dostert, L. - 855bis. Dougherty, A. O'Connell (A study of rhythmic structure in the verse of William Butler Yeats). - 856. vacant. - 857. vacant. - 858. Dougherty, R.C. (Chomsky’s revolution in linguistics). - 859. Dougherty, R.C. (Collection of articles). - 860. Dougherty, R.C. (Harris and Chomsky at the syntax semantics boundary). - 861. Drachman, G. - 862. Draganu N. (Istoria sintaxei (Storia della sintassi generale)). - 863. Drage, C.L. - 864. Drange, T. - 865. Drechsel, E.J. (Mobilian jargon: linguistic, sociocultural, and historical aspects of an American Indian lingua franca). - 866. Dreher, P. (Enclosed letters in Middle High German narr.). - 867. Driessen, F.C. - 868. Drimba, V. - 869. Droege, G.B. - 870. Droste, F.G. - 871. Drummond, C.Q. - 872. Družinin, V.G. (Raskol na Donu v konce...). - 873. Dryden, E.A. - 874. Dubois, B.L., Ornstein, J.L., and W.F. Mackey (eds.) (Internal studies of languages in contact). - 875. Ducháček, O. (Abstract of l’évolution de l’articulation linguistique du domaine esthétique du latin au français contemporain.). - 876. Duckworth, J.E. - 877. Dugan, J.R. - 878. Dujčev, I. - 879. Dunatov, Rasio - 880. Duncan, C.F. - 881. Dundas, J. - 882. Durbin, M. - 883. Durer, C. - 884. Durnovo, N.N. - 885. Duroche, L.L. - 886. Durstine, J.M. - 887. Dürmüller, U. (Narrative possibilities of the tail-rime Romance). - 888. Dvornik, F. - 889. Dyck, H.D. - 890. Dye, R.E. - 891. Dyen, I. (Collected articles on lexicostatistics). - 892. Dyen, I. (Conference on lexicostatistics-Montreal). - 893. Dyen, I. (Conference on lexicostatistics-Montreal).
    - E
      894. Earle, W.J. - 895. Eastlack, C.L. - 896. Eaton, T. (Lit. Semantics-Crucial Dec). - 897. Eaton, T. (Theoretical semantics). - 898. Eaton, T. (ed.) (I.A. Richards Festschrift). - 899. Eaton, T. (ed.) (Journal of Literary Semantics). - 900. Eaton, T. - 901. Ebel, H. - 902. Ebeling, C.L. (Semantics). - 903. Ebeling, H.A. - 904. Eberbach, M.L. - 905. Ebner, I.D. - 906. Ebneter, T. (Generative-transformational gramm. of French). - 907. Echeruo, M., and J. Chukwudalu - 908. Echerverria, M.S. (Late stages in the acquisition of Spanish syntax). - 909. Eckhardt, C. - 910. Eddleman, F.E. - 911. Eder, Z. - 912. Edie, J.M. - 913. Edie, J.M. - 914. Edmonds, M.H. (Language Acquisition and Sensori-Motor Development). - 915. Edmondson, W.J. (A model for the analysis of spoken discourse). - 916. Edmonson, M.S. (ed.) (Mayan ethnolinguistics). - 917. Edwards, P.M.H. - 918. Eekman, T., and D. Worth (Slavic poetics conference). - 919. Eekman, T., and A. Kadić (eds.) (Križanić volume). - 920. Eekman, T., and G. Hüttl-Folter (Russian-Latin 17th century lexicon). - 921. Effenberger, V. - 922. Efrat, B. - 923. Egan, E. - 924. Egan, J.J. - 925. Egert, E. - 926. Eggert, G.H. (Early Sources in aphasia and related disorders). - 927. Egri, P. - 928. Ehri, L.C., and P.R. Ammon (The development of antonym adjective structures in children). - 929. Ehrman, M.E. - 930. Ehrman, M.E. - 931. Ehrstine, J.W. (The metaphysics of Byron). - 932. Einbond, B. - 933. Eisenlohr, H.L. - 934. Eisenstein, S.A. - 935. Ekmanis, R. - 936. El-Azma, N. (Free verse in Modern Arabic literature). - 937. El-Ezabi, Y. - 938. El Sayed, D.H.A. - 939. Elerick, C. - 940. Eliopulos, J. (A rhetorical-poetic description of Beckett’s dramatic language). - 941. Elkin, B. (Miljukov, P.). - 942. Elledge, W.P. - 943. Elling, M.F. (L’oeuvre dramatique de Michel de Ghelderode). - 944. Elliot, T.J. (Complaint as a Middle English genre). - 945. Ellis, C.D. - 946. Ellis, J. - 947. Emery, M. (Modern approach to scient. Russian). - 948. Emma, R.D. - 949. Emmerich, J. (Anthony Trollope: his perception of character and the traumatic experience). - 950. Emoto, S. - 951. Encrevé, P. - 952. Endzelīns, J. - 953. Endzelīns, J. (Lettische Grammatik). - 954. Eng, J. van der - 955. Eng, J. van der (Papers on Slavic poetics and semiotics). - 956. Eng, J. van der, and M. Grygar (eds.) (Warsaw congress semiotic study of cultures). - 957. Engel, W. von Raffler (Language acquisition-the state of the arts). - 958. Engel, W. von Raffler (ed.) (Prospects in child language). - 959. Engelhardt, G. (Studies in Medieval Heuristic). - 960. Engelkamp, J. - 961. Engelkamp, J. (Über den Einfluss der semantischen Struktur auf die Verarbeitung von...). - 962. England, B., and J. Ambrosegtillet (Glossary of transformational gr.). - 963. England, P.K. - 964. Englander, A. - 965. Enkvist, N. (On Defining Style). - 966. Eoyang, E.C. (Word of mouth: oral storytelling in the Pien-wen). - 967. Epp, A.R. - 968. Erde, E. (Wittgensteinian linguistic analysis...). - 969. Erde, E.L. - 970. Erdman, E.G. Jr. - 971. Erhart, A. - 972. Erickson, J.L. - 973. Erickson, S.J. (A Reading of Goethe’s ‘Die Wahlverwandtschaften’ and Musil’s ‘Der Mann ohne Eigenschaften’). - 974. Erlenvejn, A. - 975. Erlich, V. - 976. Erlich, V. (Russian formalism). - 977. Erlich, V. (ed.) - 978. Értavy-Baráth, J.M. - 979. Essen, A.J. van (ed.) (The Acquisition of foreign languages). - 980. Estrada, C.J. - 981. Eustis, Alvin - 982. Evans, C.B. - 983. Evans, D.A.H. - 984. Evans, J.L. - 985. Evans, R.A. - 986. Evans, W.A. - 987. Evreinov, I.A. (Negation in the Russian Language system). - 988. Ewton, R.W. Jr.
    - F
      989. Faccani, R. (ed.) (Festschrift Gasparini). - 990. Fagan, D.S. - 991. Fagerlie, J.M. - 992. Fairley, I.R. (Syntactic deviance in the poetry of E.E. Cummings). - 993. Falk, T.H. (Heimito von Doderer’s concept of the novel: theory and practice.). - 994. Fall, E. - 995. Fallon, R.T. - 996. Fant, G. - 997. Fant, G. (Acoustic theory). - 998. Fantini, A.E. (Language acq. of a bilingual child). - 999. Faraci, R. - 1000. Farmer, N.K. Jr. - 1001. Farrow, A. - 1002. vacant. - 1003. Farzan, M. - 1004. Fauconnier, G. (Theoretical implications of some llobal phenomena in syntax). - 1005. Faulkner, D.R. - 1006. Fay, W.H. - 1007. Fayer, M.H. (Gide, Freedom and Dostoevsky). - 1008. Fedorov, A.I. - 1009. Feeny, T.P. - 1010. Fehderau, H.W. - 1011. Feldman, C. (Sentence meaning: a psycholinguistic view of communication). - 1012. Feldman, D.M. - 1013. Feldman, S.D. - 1014. Fennell, T.G. - 1015. Fennell, T.G. (English-French transformational-generative grammar terminology). - 1016. Ferdinandy, G. - 1017. Ferguson, C. (Language survey of Africa). - 1018. Ferguson, C.A. (Collection of articles). - 1019. Ferguson, George B. (ed.) (John Fletcher, The Woman's Prize, Or The Tamer tamed: a critical edition = Studies in English Literature, 1966). - 1020. Ferguson, M.H. - 1021. Ferguson, S.C. - 1022. Ferguson, T. -1022bis. Fernandez, G.M.A. (Prolegomenon to structural ethnosemantics). - 1023. Fernando, C. - 1024. Ferrante, J.M. - 1025. Ferrell, J.O. - 1026. Fields, B.F. - 1027. Figg, R.M. III - 1028. Filbeck, D. (T’in, A historical study). - 1029. Filips-Juswigg, K. (Zapiski o russkich: nemeckie vospominanija Vtoroj mirovoj vojny). - 1030. Fillenbaum, S. - 1031. Fillmore, C. - 1032. Fink, M.J. - 1033. Finnie, W.B. - 1034. Firchow, E. (ed.) (Haugen Festschrift). -1034bis. Firchow, E. (ed.), Maurer Festschrift. - 1035. Firestone, H.L. - 1036. Firestone, R.H. (Elements of traditional structure in the couplet epics of the late MHG Dietrich Cycle). - 1037. Fischer-Jörgensen, E. (Selected writings). - 1038. Fisher, B.J. - 1039. Fisher, J. - 1040. Fisher, J. - 1041. Fisher, J.A. (On being guided by a rule: some reflections on a conceptual problem in Chomsky’s theory of syntax). - 1042. Fisher, J.C. - 1043. Fisher, M.A. - 1044. Fishman, J. - 1045. Fishman, J. (General). - 1046. Fishman, J. (Introd. Textbk. Sociolinguist.). - 1047. Fisiak, J. - 1047bis. Fisiak, J. (1972). - 1048. Fitch, P.M. - 1049. Fitzpatrick, A.M. (The comic encounter in West Africa). - 1050. Flaherty, M.G. - 1051. Fleischhauer, I. (Elemente einer russichen Aufklärung: N.N. Strachov). - 1052. Fletcher, P. (Experimental approach to syntactic paraphrase). - 1053. Fletcher, R.M. - 1054. Fletcher, R.M. - 1055. Flier, M.S. - 1056. Flier, M.S. (ed.). - 1057. Flores d’Arcais, G.B. - 1058. vacant. - 1059. Florovsky, A. - 1060. Florovsky, G.V. - 1061. Flower, D.S. - 1062. Fodale, P. - 1063. Fodor, A. - 1064. Fodor, I. (On film synchronization). - 1065. Fodor, I. - 1066. Fodor, J.A. (Collected works). - 1067. vacant. - 1068. Fodor, J.D. (Collected works). - 1069. Fogelman, R.H. - 1070. Fokker, A.A., and E. Smolikowska (Anatomy of a word class). - 1071. Folb, E.A. - 1072. vacant. - 1073. Folejewski, Z. - 1074. Folejewski, Z. (ed.) (Canadian Contributions to the 7th International Congress of Slavists). - 1075. Folsom, M.H. - 1076. vacant. - 1077-1079. Fónagy, I. - 1080. vacant. - 1081. Fónagy, I. (Fust Milan: Oregseg). - 1082. vacant. - 1083. Fónagy, I. (La voix du poète (The voice of the poet)). - 1084. Fónagy, I. (La vive voix). - 1085. Ford, G.B. (Isidore of Seville: on grammar). - 1086. Ford, G.B. (The Old Lithuanian catechism of Martynas Mažvydas (1547)). - 1087. Ford, G.B., Jr. (Old Lith. Cat. Vilentas). - 1088. Forrest, W. (Vowel alliteration). - 1089. Forslund, D.E.C. - 1090. Forster, K. I. - 1091. Forsyth, J. - 1092. Fort, M.C. - 1093. Fortune, R. (The trilogy of A.V. Sukhovo-Kobylin). - 1094. Foster, J.M. - 1095. Foster, M.L. - 1096. Foster, S.M. - 1097. Fougeres, R.G. - 1098. Fought, J.G. - 1099. Foulkes, A.P. - 1100. Fowler, D. - 1101-1102. Fowler, R. - 1102bis. - Fox, Allan B. (The prosody of the non-pentameter line in Tudor drama). - 1103. Fox, L. (Caucasian linguistics project). - 1104. Fraenkel, G. - 1105. Fraenkel, M. - 1106. Frake, C.O. - 1107. Francis, E.D. - 1108. vacant. - 1109. Francis, H.E. - 1110. Francq, H. - 1111. Franek, J. - 1112. Frank, J. - 1113. Frankart, J.D. - 1114. Franks, J.R. - 1115. Frauenrath, M. - 1116. Frazier, H. - 1117. Fredeman, P.H. (Ben Jonson: principles of criticism and creation). - 1118. Frederic, M. (La répétition.). - 1119. Freeman, D.C. - 1120. Freeman, L.C. - 1121. Freidin, R. (Interpretive semantics and the syntax). - 1122. French, A. - 1123. French, R.W. - 1124. Friedl, B.C. - 1125. Friedl, B.C. (Language and the goals of man). - 1126. Friedl, B.C. (Linguistic research at T.T.). - 1127. Friedman, J.B. - 1128. Friedrich, P.W. - 1129. Friedrichsmeyer, E.M. - 1130. Friend, J.H. - 1131. Fries, P.H. - 1132. Frink, Orrin - 1133. vacant. - 1134. Fromkin, V.A. (Collection of articles). - 1135. Fromkin, V.A. (Collection of articles). - 1136. Fromkin, V.A. (Performance and competence). - 1137. Fromkin, V.A. (Speech errors as linguistic evidence). - 1138. Fromkin, V.A. - 1139. Fromkin, V.A. - 1140. Defromont, Hubert J. - 1141. Frumkina, R.M. - 1142. Frumkina, R.M. (Verojatnost’ èlementov teksta i rečevoe povedenie). - 1143. Fry, D.K. Jr. - 1144. Fuchs, A. (Morphologie des verbs im Cahuilla). - 1145. Fudge, E.C. - 1146. Fugazy, I.M. - 1147. Fujiwara, Y. - 1148. Fulcher, E.S. - 1149. Fuller, R. - 1150. Fullerton, G.L. (Historical Germanic verb morphology). - 1151. Fuqua, M.M. - 1152. Furnée, E.J. - 1153. Furrow, D.J.N. (The Two Si’s of Italian).